<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dasein on JUF</title>
    <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/series/dasein/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dasein on JUF</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 13:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://johnurquhartferguson.info/series/dasein/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dasein - Chapter 5 - Authenticity</title>
      <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-chapter-5-authenticity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-chapter-5-authenticity/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I assume you think of me as unreal,&amp;rdquo; said the figure. &amp;ldquo;That I am merely a character from your story. I am sure, then, that it will come as a shock to find out that you are only half correct.&amp;rdquo;
Martin had lost all feeling in his body. All he could do was look on and listen to the figure&amp;rsquo;s distorted voice.
&amp;ldquo;You see, Martin, I am not real. My actions are not under my control at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dasein - Chapter 4 - Confrontation</title>
      <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-chapter-4-confrontation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-chapter-4-confrontation/</guid>
      <description>Martin felt his throat become thick and heavy, but managed to open his mouth and confront the killer.
&amp;ldquo;Do not leave,&amp;rdquo; Martin told the figure. &amp;ldquo;I am your creator. You have entered into my world and you have no place here. You must not run. I must destroy you before you damage this universe.&amp;rdquo;
The figure began to speak in a distorted voice. It did not come from his mouth. It seemed to come from everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dasein - Chapter 3 - Pursuit</title>
      <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-chapter-3-pursuit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 16:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-chapter-3-pursuit/</guid>
      <description>As soon as Martin admitted to himself that he was powerless, he was released. He sat up in bed, waiting to see if he had the will to move around. The restrictions seemed to be gone. He wondered if it was really true though.
If he did not have the control to break fictional bonds on him, how could he be sure someone was not controlling him now? Perhaps someone was anticipating all the movements he wanted to make, then making them for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dasein - Chapter 2 - Invention</title>
      <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-chapter-2-invention/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-chapter-2-invention/</guid>
      <description>Martin sat in his kitchen looking dazed and confused. He coddled his warm mug of coffee in his hands and tried not to think about what was happening. Instead, he tried to think about what he was going to do at the weekend, but immediately felt uneasy. He tried to think of nothing at all and simply stare into space but he could not get the images out of his mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dasein - Chapter 1 - Discovery</title>
      <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-chapter-1-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-chapter-1-discovery/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it can be hard to tell when the present began. It seems easy to remember the past and plan for the future, but when does the current become just a memory? When do your visions of tomorrow have life thrust into them and become the immediate part of your linear existence? Is your experience just a series of present moments or is it the totality of all the moments past?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dasein - Preface</title>
      <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-preface/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-preface/</guid>
      <description>A Dasein is a being in the world. The Dasein recognizes the place one has in time and space: that all beings are linked together with their Universe, their Being. They are all part of the one.
The Dasein will acknowledge his fate. He knows that he has no will of his own. He is a product of his environment and his Being. The Dasein must be authentic to himself or he will never be at peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dasein - Dedication</title>
      <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-dedication/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/dasein-dedication/</guid>
      <description>For whoever reads this, my story is dedicated to you. You are likely to be one of a small number of people who will ever find these words, so I thank you for taking the time to do so and for keeping my characters alive.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>