<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thought-Factory on JUF</title>
    <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/blogseries/thought-factory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thought-Factory on JUF</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 23:45:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://johnurquhartferguson.info/blogseries/thought-factory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Thought Factory - Self Reliance and Waiting for Permission</title>
      <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/thought-factory-self-reliance-and-waiting-for-permission/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 23:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/thought-factory-self-reliance-and-waiting-for-permission/</guid>
      <description>I have another cinema story for you. My local film theatre has an option called &amp;lsquo;VIP.&amp;rsquo; In addition to the improved seating and unlimited snacks, your ticket grants access to a pre-film, all-you-can-eat buffet. After getting my money&amp;rsquo;s worth much quicker than expected, I had a good half hour to enjoy before I would be needed in the cinema hall. I decided to spend the time visiting the water closet in the hopes of securing a more settled and comfortable experience while the film was showing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thought Factory - Cinema Etiquette and the Suspension of Disbelief</title>
      <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/thought-factory-cinema-etiquette-and-the-suspension-of-disbelief/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/thought-factory-cinema-etiquette-and-the-suspension-of-disbelief/</guid>
      <description>I saw a horror film last weekend at the cinema. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to take movies for granted with the near constant access we have to them: Phones, laptops, televisions, virtual reality home theatres, mixed reality projections into the sky&amp;hellip; At any given moment most of us have immediate access to films but, at least for me, these options tend to encourage casual viewing. When it&amp;rsquo;s so easy to have a film playing wherever I am, I tend to have it playing in the background.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>