<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Musings-on-Writing on JUF</title>
    <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/blogseries/musings-on-writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Musings-on-Writing on JUF</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 20:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://johnurquhartferguson.info/blogseries/musings-on-writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings on Writing - 2018 Year in Review</title>
      <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/musings-on-writing-2018-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/musings-on-writing-2018-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m alive! You might not believe me, but I totally am.
Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s been a year since I posted anything here. Yes, the last thing I posted was the previous year&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Year in Review.&amp;rsquo; Yes, I can list agreements&amp;hellip; but I did lots of stuff this year&amp;hellip; LOTS of stuff!
It is disappointing that I didn&amp;rsquo;t post more. You would be correct in thinking that this is representative of my writing output for the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings on Writing - 2017 Year in Review</title>
      <link>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/musings-on-writing-2017-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnurquhartferguson.info/post/musings-on-writing-2017-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>Greetings, Programs! During my Christmas break, I took some time to reflect on my previous year of writing. It was in December 2016 that I first decided to rework my writing setup and, one year later, I was considering whether I&amp;rsquo;d achieved my goals.
Actually, there were only two goals: write more, and write better. The problem is that I&amp;rsquo;m a classic yak shaver. On my way to achieving those goals I determined that I needed new writing software, new website software, the ability to easily publish to multiple formats, a dedicated writing computer, a new computer keyboard, a writing bag, a marketing strategy, a better choice of fonts for both writing and publishing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>